Conor McKeon

Ireland native with a Master's degree in Biology. Having worked for one year in a biotechnology industry, I'm excited to dive back into the specialty coffee industry, interacting with people in a vibrant, fast-paced environment and applying my high level of customer service and professionalism. In my next role I'm keen to learn as much as I can about coffee and I'm interested to gain management experience. I'm a creative and ambitious person and I enjoy working collaboratively on projects and exchanging ideas.

EXPERIENCE

☐ Fitzpatrick's Irish Bar

Montpellier, FR

Barman.

☐ Aran Irish Pub

Sep 2021 - May 2021

Sep 2021 - May 2022

Amsterdam, NL

Barman and food service.

□ Scoom Delight

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

Berlin, DE

Preparing coffee and serving food to customers through German.

□ Darwin's Ltd. Café

Aug 2019 — Oct 2019

Boston, USA

Specialty coffee barista, cashier, preparing and serving meals, cleaning.

□ Super Duper Burgers

May 2018 — Aug 2018

California, USA

Fast food service with a focus on efficiency, safety and hygiene.

☐ 895 Park Ave

May 2017 — Aug 2017

New York, USA

Doorman for the residential building at 895 Park Ave.

☐ McCambridges

Sep 2016 — May 2017

Galway, IE

Porter and dishwasher in a busy restaurant kitchen.



- Berlin
- +32 470 11 48 58
- conor.mckeon4@gmail.com
- http://www.linkedin.com/in/mckeon-conor

English native language (C2)

French fluent (C1)

German beginner (A2)

QUALITIES

- Passionate about creating great customer experiences
- A keen interest in coffee
- Can work early shifts (6.30am)
- Positive attitude
- Fast learner
- Organized
- Task focused
- · Efficient multitasker
- Punctual

EDUCATION

MSc. Health-Biology 2020 - 2022University of Montpellier Mention Très Bien (1st Class Honours)

BSc. Chemistry University of Galway 1st Class Honours

2015 - 2019